The receptionist has asked us if we have any questions and we may have several.
接待员问我们是否有任何问题，我们可能有几个问题。
I know when I want to stay at a hotel for the first time I usually have quite a few questions and sometimes
我知道当我第一次想住在酒店时，我通常有很多问题，有时
I will book a room on the phone because I have questions I don't want to book online sometimes because
我会通过电话预订房间，因为我有一些问题不想在线预订，有时因为
I want to ask some of these important questions so let's explore a few of them.
我想问一些重要的问题，所以让我们来探讨其中的一些。
Of course there could be many more.
当然可能还有更多。
What are the gym hours and when is breakfast.
健身房的营业时间是几点，早餐是什么时候。
OK now gym hours.
好的，现在健身房时间。
That means when is the gym open.
这意味着健身房什么时候开放。
Maybe.
也许。
Maybe you like to work out or you like to have a workout and when you travel it's very important for
也许你喜欢锻炼或者你喜欢锻炼，当你旅行时，这对你来说非常重要
you to exercise.
你去锻炼。
So you need to go to the gym in the hotel.
所以你需要去酒店的健身房。
OK so you want to know when you can and when you can't and when is breakfast What time is breakfast
好的，所以你想知道什么时候可以，什么时候不能，什么时候吃早餐 什么时候吃早餐
served.
服务。
I want to mention something really quickly about this w o r o UTI and w o k o u t one word or two words.
我想很快提到一些关于这个 w o r o UTI 的事情，并且只用一两个词。
Well it depends on how we're using it.
好吧，这取决于我们如何使用它。
We could say workout as one word if we use it as one word then it's a noun.
如果我们将锻炼作为一个词使用，那么它就是一个名词。
If we say it as two words then now it's a phrase all verb and it's the same for example for take off
如果我们把它说成两个词，那么现在它是一个短语，都是动词，例如起飞
and take off those two words.
并去掉这两个字。
That's a phrase all verb phrase a verb usually has a preposition and a verb together first it's a verb
这是一个短语所有动词短语一个动词通常有一个介词和一个动词一起首先它是一个动词
than a preposition or a verb followed by an adverb and there are many phrases verbs you can learn them
而不是介词或动词后跟副词，并且有很多短语动词你可以学习它们
on your own.
靠自己。
Very important to learn them though because they're a very important part of spoken English or take
学习它们非常重要，因为它们是英语口语非常重要的一部分
off and that becomes a noun.
关闭，这成为一个名词。
How would we use these.
我们将如何使用这些。
Well the plane will take off in ten minutes.
那么飞机将在十分钟后起飞。
That's an action that's going to happen.
这是即将发生的行动。
So we should use the phrase will verb.
所以我们应该使用短语will动词。
Two words however when the plane does take off and then we're able to take off our seat belts.
两个字，但是当飞机起飞时，我们就可以解下安全带了。
Different Meaning of takeoff.
起飞的不同含义。
Then we could say we took off our seatbelts after takeoff and now takeoff is being used as a noun because
然后我们可以说我们在起飞后取下了安全带，现在起飞被用作名词，因为
it's an event after this event happened so before takeoff and after takeoff.
这是该事件发生之后的事件，因此在起飞之前和起飞之后。
Now the plane will take off phrase a verb.
现在飞机会起飞短语动词。
Same here.
同样在这里。
Workout after my workout my workout.
锻炼后锻炼我的锻炼。
How is your workout.
你的锻炼怎么样。
It was very good.
非常好。
My workout my workout was very good.
我的锻炼我的锻炼非常好。
I need to work out every day to stay sane to stay happy.
我需要每天锻炼以保持理智以保持快乐。
I need to work out every day.
我需要每天锻炼。
So this one phrase a verb this one now.
所以这个短语现在变成动词这个。
Basically that's how it works.
基本上就是这样。
There are lots of examples like that.
有很多这样的例子。
I just wanted to mention it quickly.
我只是想快速提一下。
OK so answer breakfast is included with your room.
好的，所以回答早餐包含在您的房间内。
I didn't ask that question but it's useful information.
我没有问这个问题，但这是有用的信息。 这意味着我不需要支付额外费用。
Maybe the standard room doesn't have breakfast included.
也许标准间不包括早餐。
Maybe I need to pay extra for breakfast.
也许我需要为早餐支付额外费用。
That's a big extra cost.
这是一笔很大的额外费用。
OK so it's nice to have the deluxe room because breakfast is included remember that means it's part
好的，所以有豪华房很好，因为包括早餐，记住这意味着它是一部分
of the cost of the room and that's from 7:00 a.m. to 11:00 a.m..
房间的费用，从早上 7:00 到 11:00。
Now you could say 7:00 to 11:00 a.m. And that would be fine too.
现在你可以说早上 7:00 到 11:00。那也可以。
Could we say between 7 and 11:00 a.m..
我们可以说在上午 7 点到 11:00 之间吗？
Of course of course.
当然当然。
We've learned that by now.
我们现在已经学会了。
All right.
好的。
The gym is always open.
健身房总是开放的。
We could also say if something is always open 24 7 sometimes it's written like that sometimes it's written
我们也可以说，如果某事总是 24 7 开放，有时它是这样写的，有时它是这样写的
like that.
像那样。
What does that mean.
这意味着什么。
People often ask me what does 24/7 mean.
人们经常问我 24/7 是什么意思。
Well it means 24 hours a day 24 days a week 24/7.
好吧，这意味着每周 24 天，每天 24 小时，每天 24 小时，每天 24 小时。
That means it's always open.
这意味着它始终是开放的。
It's never closed.
它永远不会关闭。
So that one is very common you often will see that in front of things like convenience stores.
所以那个很常见，你经常会在便利店之类的东西面前看到它。
We can also say the gym is always open so you don't need to worry about that.
我们也可以说健身房总是开放的，所以你不必担心。
No need to worry about that you can go to the gym at 2:00 a.m. If you want.
如果您愿意，无需担心您可以在凌晨 2:00 去健身房。
Will you be needing transportation from the airport.
你需要从机场来的交通工具吗？
OK this one is asking basically are you flying in.
好的，这个基本上是在问你在飞吗？
And if so do you need a way to get to the hotel from the airport.
如果是这样，您是否需要一种从机场到酒店的方法。
If you're coming from another city you could be driving.
如果你来自另一个城市，你可能会开车。
If so you wouldn't need transportation from the airport.
如果是这样，您将不需要从机场接送。
You could if you're flying in take another type of transportation like a taxi but maybe this hotel offers
如果您乘坐飞机，您可以乘坐出租车等其他交通工具，但也许这家酒店提供
a shuttle service.
班车服务。
It's often called the airport shuttle S H U T T L E service which is just back and forth like this offered
它通常被称为机场班车 S H U T T L E 服务，就像这样来回提供
by maybe a specific hotel and the airport shuttle.
也许是特定的酒店和机场班车。
The difference between that and a bus is generally that a shuttle only does this and only has two stops.
这和公共汽车的区别通常是班车只做这个，而且只有两站。
Hotel.
酒店。
Airport hotel.
机场酒店。
Airport.
飞机场。
Whereas a bus usually stops along the way.
而公共汽车通常会在途中停下来。
Church makes all the stops.
教会竭尽全力。
That's the general difference.
这就是普遍的区别。
OK so that's the answer to the question.
好的，这就是问题的答案。
Now let's get into the shuttle situation and how much that will cost.
现在让我们进入航天飞机的情况以及这将花费多少。
If we do want to get the airport shuttle.
如果我们确实想乘坐机场班车。
If we're flying into a city and we're planning to stay at a hotel we often need to get to the hotel
如果我们飞往一个城市并且我们计划住在酒店，我们经常需要到达酒店
which is usually downtown but usually the airport is rather far away from downtown.
这通常在市中心，但通常机场离市中心很远。
Most of the time airports are not in the middle of the city although sometimes they are.
大多数时候机场不在城市中心，尽管有时它们在。
Which is interesting and very convenient for people flying but maybe not for local people.
这对飞行的人来说很有趣也很方便，但对当地人来说可能不是。
So we've been asked if we need transportation from the airport to the hotel.
所以我们被问到是否需要从机场到酒店的交通服务。
That suggests that they offer it but we should still confirm.
这表明他们提供了它，但我们仍然应该确认。
Yes actually yes actually means I do need that sort of transportation.
是的，实际上是的，实际上意味着我确实需要那种交通工具。
This is the guest.
这是客人。
This is the receptionist and this is the guest.
这是接待员，这是客人。
Yes.
是的。
In fact we use actually when we want to say this is the reality.
事实上，当我们想说这就是现实时，我们会使用实际。
Actually I'm really really hungry.
其实我真的很饿。
For example do you offer shuttle service shuttle service.
例如，您是否提供接送服务接送服务。
You can call it that.
你可以这样称呼它。
And if so how much is it.
如果是的话，多少钱。
We often use this if so structure to ask a question about one thing.
我们经常使用这种 if so 结构来询问关于一件事的问题。
If the answer is yes before we get the yes answer.
如果答案是肯定的，在我们得到肯定的答案之前。
So for example do you have a vegetarian menu.
例如，你有素食菜单吗？
Vegetarian means someone who doesn't eat meat.
素食者是指不吃肉的人。
If so could I look at it please.
如果是这样，我可以看看它。
If the answer is yes could I please look at the vegetarian menu.
如果答案是肯定的，我可以看看素食菜单。
Do you have that.
你有吗。
If so could I look at it.
如果是这样我可以看看它。
That's before I get the answer yes because maybe it's yes maybe it's no.
那是在我得到答案之前是的，因为也许是的，也许不是。
It's a very useful very useful way of asking questions.
这是一种非常有用的提问方式。
Actually it's complementary.
其实是互补的。
Now this complementary is often used by hotels and restaurants.
现在酒店和餐馆经常使用这种补充。
A lot of customer service or service oriented businesses too mean free.
许多客户服务或面向服务的业务也意味着免费。
Basically it means free.
基本上它意味着免费。
Oh sir that is actually complimentary.
哦，先生，这实际上是免费的。
We would like to give you this towel complimentary this complimentary towel with our logo on it to remember
我们想为您免费赠送这条毛巾，这条免费毛巾上印有我们的标志，以供记住
your stay here.
你留在这里。
Whatever it's complimentary maybe a complimentary breakfast is a free breakfast and it's sort of a fancy
不管它是免费的，也许免费早餐就是免费早餐，而且有点花哨
way more formal way of saying it's free.
说它是免费的更正式的方式。
If we say yes we have free shuttle service.
如果我们同意，我们将提供免费班车服务。
It just sounds a little maybe a little cheap although it is the same meaning the shuttle leaves every
只是听起来有点便宜，虽然它的含义是一样的，穿梭每
hour on the hour.
小时。
If we say every hour that could be a little confusing because that could be 10 20 11 20 12 20.
如果我们说每小时可能会有点令人困惑，因为那可能是 10 20 11 20 12 20。
Right.
正确的。
What we want to say is when we say every hour on the hour leaves at 11:00 it leaves at 12:00.
我们想说的是，当我们说每小时在 11:00 离开时，它在 12:00 离开。
It leaves at 1.
它在 1 点离开。
It leaves at 2 on the hour doesn't leave it doesn't leave at eleven 10 it doesn't leave at 11:00 0 5
整点 2 点出发 不出发 11 点不出发 10 点出发 11:00 不出发 0 5
it leaves at eleven and if you miss the eleven you need to take the 12:00 12:00 p.m. for example.
它在 11 点出发，如果您错过了 11 点，您需要乘坐 12:00 12:00 p.m.例如。
So just look for the one what the shuttle.
因此，只需寻找那个穿梭的东西。
The shuttle is often used to replace the word bus means the bus can look for the one with the unbuilt
穿梭常用于代替“巴士”一词，意思是巴士可以寻找未建成的那辆
hotel logo in the parking lot in front of terminal to terminal 2 T2 sometimes T1 T2 terminal is the
酒店标志在航站楼前的停车场到 2 号航站楼 T2 有时 T1 T2 航站楼是
long area where all the planes are.
所有飞机所在的长区域。
OK great.
好，很好。
That's a way to say Awesome fantastic because nothing else needs to be done right.
这是一种说“太棒了”的方式，因为没有其他事情需要做对了。
If I really want to take a taxi when I get there I can.
如果我真的想在到达那里时乘坐出租车，我可以。
But now I know that I don't need to arrange the shuttle service.
但现在我知道我不需要安排接送服务了。
It's just there and it leaves every hour on the hour so I don't need to do anything else here.
它就在那里，它每小时都会离开，所以我不需要在这里做任何其他事情。
I have this information I'm done.
我有这个信息我已经完成了。
That's my question.
那是我的问题。
I'm finished.
我完成了。